0:00:00.000,0:00:00.150
0:00:00.000,0:00:00.150
If you have any questions, please click here: Click here to go to:
तेला दाला taka दीना में: dra taba taba ki dina dina pada anta थीi में: dra eika थी है हैवा
0:00:00.150,0:00:00.300
0:00:00.150,0:00:00.300
Aba an: d: A name is used as: to search the language: If you want to go to the next page, then go to:
अबा ए: डी: एक नमक जबा यू: हा इधरहरधर यूट: हे जी है: थि ईका हामा जबा हू है तब ईका थाई हाजारा था दारा जिंहेन:
0:00:00.300,0:00:00.450
0:00:00.300,0:00:00.450
The name of the person's name will be shared with the person as follows: In order to have a good understanding of the language: d: A good friend of the person who is present at the place where he is present,
शमीला विचित्र ना घारा जा गौरी राहे भी राहा आगा इन: चा पैरा हामा उत्तरा धर्म अबा ए: डी: एक भी घ्हा ध्यान आभा घ प्रबन्धा था आधा का जाता अत्याधिका शामीला या देति
0:00:00.450,0:00:01.000
0:00:00.450,0:00:01.000
This is the one that has: d: to make a list: that means you can enter it: I want to know how to use it.
ईका है तब एचआई काए ए: डी: एक राहेनी तका हर है: केआई वर्क्सिडी जबा हामा अन्ता दीना डी: इम्बा इधरहरधर बाहारा विवाहा
0:00:01.000,0:00:01.150
0:00:01.000,0:00:01.150
I do not want to give a name for this purpose but I do not want to get it.
हू है वाहा घर बाहारा ना है ईका इसा कर देती ईका अनुदान ईका जिना है
0:00:01.150,0:00:01.300
0:00:01.150,0:00:01.300
pahun: chaa vidaa aan: ta mein: gha hai taba ki eijein: t: a koo shahta hai apne tha in: It is where we go: When we go to the left, we can make it clear: And there are many things:
पहुन: चा विदा आन: टा मीन: घ है है कि खया ईजिन: टी: एक कू शूटहा है वाहा थि इन: द है हैहा है: है है वाहा जाबा तका वा अपघाट: एना दीहा की बन: सा हैन:
0:00:01.300,0:00:01.450
0:00:01.300,0:00:01.450
kiit: a eika hai mukta in: d: iyana dhurva haha ​​haha ​​haha ​​haha ​​haha ​​haha ​​pahalei hama hava hain hain: yuddha jaba bhaara hata khapata taka taka
कीट: एक ईका है मुक्ता इन: डी: इयान ध्रुव है हर जिगाह तुमा हामा पहलेई हामा आरा जबा हम अब है: युद्ध जबा भर खापता तबका
0:00:01.450,0:00:02.000
0:00:01.450,0:00:02.000
If you want to go to a shop with the help of this, then you can go to: Here are some of the things that you have to visit:
ईका पडा गार्डना दारा तका है है फलाता वा तका जबा यू: हा दुर्बला इन भरा पडा कू हामा फाला माई यू: हा है अब है है
0:00:02.000,0:00:02.150
0:00:02.000,0:00:02.150
Do not forget to do this: joo huun: taka unhein: gund ~ a brxn: hand ~ a
देहा हिई फा है है राखा है: जू हुन: तका अनहेन: गुंड ~ ए ब्रक्सन: हाथ ~ ए
0:00:02.150,0:00:02.300
0:00:02.150,0:00:02.300
hoo eivan: vaha baahara va hu ek kei hai ekika Bharatata hai hu hai ham tiina hai hai ran: ga bharxn: ga thii
हू ईवन: वाहा बहरा वा हू ईका केई लिई ईका भारत है उड्डीपका है हामा तिआना है जबा एचआईआई रन: गा बिहरन: गा थि
0:00:02.300,0:00:02:450
0:00:02.300,0:00:02:450
Aba ga haan: I do not want to go anywhere, but I do not know where to look at: I do not know how many people are there
अबा गा हान: लिई रुपए खाई लिई राहा हजुरा है वाहा वाहा अता ईका प्रधान इन: चा है है जबा है ईका हारा जीआई हला घ है ना इन: ड्रि भिदा
0:00:02.450,0:00:03.000
0:00:02.450,0:00:03.000
Aba taka d: If you want to go to the place where it is located, then go to the top of the page, then go to the place where it is called: t: There is always a place where you are staying where you are staying.
अबा तका डी: इम्बा जबा उधारा तका हर आना धन है अता है तब घा ईका घरा ध्रुव है वाहा जाता घारा इतिहासा ईजिन: टी: एक है वाहा फिरा रहेई उललेखा है वाहा रहेई थीई
0:00:03.000,0:00:03.150
0:00:03.000,0:00:03.150
I have been there: they are: I do not know what they are: They are the only people I know: I want to go
हला है घा मेरा: है मुन: गा उरदा आपा हमा रहेहे है: वेई जबा खा ii patra kampa hain: taka para khuuna eika है
0:00:03.150,0:00:03.300
0:00:03.150,0:00:03.300
Do not do this: eivan: it is hrxdaya
भाव ना मेरा: ईवन: घ है हैक्सडे है
0:00:03.300,0:00:03.450
0:00:03.300,0:00:03.450
I do not even want to comment as much as they are saying: they are too much: they are: jinhein: kharcha
है ना है भी ईका क्रमा असगंध भी इधर हला हैथा है: तात्त्व घ है भी है: कथ हन: जिन्हेन: खारचा है
0:00:03.450,0:00:04.000
0:00:03.450,0:00:04.000
You have to: try to go to the top of the page: If you have any questions, please contact us here: please contact us at any time: Do not translate: it is a different form
है वाहा है: कफ घारा धाना घी अपाराण: टा हू है याहा हलका जटा था जान: गैली शमीला आजी की ढना मेरा: दलाहानी टी: हायका है वाहा फिरा है